

ANN-SOFI JÖNSSON

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a frontend developer with experience in retail, writing and running. For me, programming is about three things: Creativity, Structure and Curiosity!

I have always been creative and like coming up with ideas and making things from scratch. It could be everything from a serious article to a funny poem for a friend's birthday. At the same time, I am an organized person who likes to have my ducks in a row.

TECH SKILLS

HTML CSS JavaScript React Redux Node.js Mongodb Github Terminal Flexbox Postman

SKILLS

Communication Leadership Teamwork Agile Freelance journalism Creativity

CONTACT INFO

Phone: +46 733 602828

Email: annsofi.jonsson@hotmail.se Portfolio: https://annsofi-jonsson-

portfolio.netlify.app/

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/annsofijonsson/

PROJECTS

TODO APP

A web-app built using React, Redux. https://todo-app-2021.netlify.app/ (Best viewed in mobile)

FRIENDS QUIZ

A mob programming project built with React & Redux. https://friends-quiz-2021.netlify.app/

FOR MORE, SEE MY PORTFOLIO:

https://annsofi-jonsson-portfolio.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

TECHNIGO BOOTCAMP

Frontend developer | Jan 2021 - present, graudate June 2021

A fast-paced remote tech educations with sprints focused on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux and Node.js. Every week we build one project either alone or during pair-/mob programming.

HALMSTAD UNIVERSITY

B.A in Media- & Communication | Aug 2004 - Jun 2007

The educations involved planning, implementing and evaluating various forms of communications projects in the area of internal communication. Also profiling, branding, issuess magagement and option of formation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IDUNA AB

Product- & Buyer assistant | Okt 2019 - present

My responsibilities include placing orders and delivery monitoring working with Relex & Microsoft Dynamix AX. Assist product manager with e.g., products, campaigns. Collaborate with other departments such as marketing and warehouse and also internal and external communication.

IDUNA AB

Quality assurance | Feb 2008 - Sept 2019

I led and developed the quality control department where performed both practical and administrative tasks. The position has meant that I have had the opportunity to improve, develop and streamline work processes with good results.